Rose Gerlach Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Magritte, Rene, 1898-1967 (7 slides) (Box 5)
  - Iolas gallery, 1965 (Box 5)
  - Byron gallery, 1968 (Box 5)
- Mallory (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - Stable gallery, 1966 (Box 5)
- Mallory (5 slides) (Box 5)
  - Alan Stone gallery, 1966 (Box 5)
- Malloy, Mike (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - O.K. Harris (Box 5)
- Manacher (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - Bodley gallery, 1970 (Box 5)
- Mandel, John, b. 1941 (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Hutchinson gallery, 1971 (Box 5)
- Mandelbaum, Rene (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1969 (Box 5)
- Mangione, Pat (9 slides) (Box 5)
  - F. Rehn gallery, 1968 (Box 5)
- Mangold, Robert, b. 1937 (5 slides) (Box 5)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1970, 1973 (Box 5)
- Mangold, Silvia Plimack, b. 1938 (4 slides) (Box 5)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1974, 1981, 1983 (Box 5)
- Mann (4 slides) (Box 5)
  - D'Arcy gallery, 1965 (Box 5)
- Manning, John (6 slides) (Box 5)
  - Graham gallery, 1970, 1971 (Box 5)
- Manso, Leo (5 slides) (Box 5)
  - Rose Fried gallery, 1968 (Box 5)
- Manzoni, Piero, 1933-1963 (5 slides) (Box 5)
  - Sonnabend gallery, 1972 (Box 5)
- Marden, Brice, b. 1938 (6 slides) (Box 5)
  - Bykert gallert, 1969, 1970 (Box 5)
- Margin (10 slides) (Box 5)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1965, 1967 (Box 5)
- Maril (8 slides) (Box 5)
  - Forum gallery, 1965 (Box 5)
- Maril, Herman, 1908-1986 (16 slides) (Box 5)
  - Forum gallery, 1968, 1971 (Box 5)
- Mark, Phyllis (22 slides) (Box 5)
  - Ruth White gallery, 1966, 1968 (Box 5)
- Markman, Ronald (17 slides) [Slide box 29] (Box 5)
  - Dintenfass gallery, 1965, 1966, 1968 (Box 5)
- Markowitz, Paul (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - Feigen gallery, 1971 (Box 5)
- Marsicano, Nicholas, 1914-1991 (11 slides) (Box 5)
  - Sachs gallery, 1971, 1972, 1973 (Box 5)
- Martens (9 slides) (Box 5)
  - Castagno gallery, 1965 (Box 5)
- Martin, Agnes, 1912-2004 (10 slides) (Box 5)
  - Elkon gallery, 1966, 1969 (Box 5)
  - Pace gallery, 1976 (Box 5)
- Martin, Alex (9 slides) (Box 5)
  - Graham gallery, 1971 (Box 5)
  - Pace gallery, 1980, 1983 (Box 5)
- Martin, Knox, b. 1923 (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1966 (Box 5)
  - Bonino gallery, 1972 (Box 5)
- Martin, Tony (5 slides) (Box 5)
  - Wise gallery, 1968 (Box 5)
- Maryan, Maryan S., 1927-1977 (4 slides) (Box 5)
  - Frumkin gallery, 1966 (Box 5)
- Masaaki (14 slides) (Box 5)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1966, 1969 (Box 5)
- Matisse, Paul (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - Wise gallery, 1968 (Box 5)
- Matta, Roberto, 1911-2002 (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - Cordier-Ekstrom gallery, 1966 (Box 5)
- Matthews, Gene (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - James Yu gallery, 1973 (Box 5)
- Mattox (5 slides) (Box 5)
  - Wise gallery, 1965, 1967 (Box 5)
- Maurer (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - Schaeffer gallery, 1969 (Box 5)
- Mauroudis, Demetrius (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1972 (Box 5)
- Mayhew (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Midtown gallery, 1971 (Box 5)
- McCartin, Jan, b. 1909 (7 slides) (Box 5)
  - Roko gallery, 1966 (Box 5)
- McChesney, Robert Pearson, b. 1913 (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - XX West gallery, 1965 (Box 5)
- McClanahan (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - Wise gallery, 1968 (Box 5)
- McClusky (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Banfer gallery, 1966 (Box 5)
- McCracken, John, b. 1934 (6 slides) (Box 5)
  - Willard gallery, 1970 (Box 5)
  - Elkon gallery, 1968, 1969, 1972 (Box 5)
- McEwen (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - Byron gallery, 1967 (Box 5)
- McGarrell, James, b. 1930 (4 slides) (Box 5)
  - Frumkin gallery, 1966 (Box 5)
- McIver, Loren (6 slides) (Box 5)
  - Matisse gallery, 1966 (Box 5)
- McLean, Richard Thorpe, b. 1934 (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1971 (Box 5)
- McMorley (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - Stefanotty gallery, 1973 (Box 5)
- McNarr (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Daniels gallery, 1965 (Box 5)
- McNeil, George J., 1908-1995 (5 slides) (Box 5)
  - Wise gallery, 1964, 1967 (Box 5)
- McGarrell, James, b. 1930 (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Frumkin gallery, 1969 (Box 5)
- Meadmore, Clement, 1929-2005 (8 slides) (Box 5)
  - Byron gallery, 1967 (Box 5)
  - Hutchinson gallery, 1971 (Box 5)
- Mehring, Howard William, 1931-1978 (10 slides) (Box 5)
  - Sachs gallery, 1966, 1968, 1970 (Box 5)
- Meigs, Walter, 1918-1988 (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Nordness gallery, 1964 (Box 5)
- Meisel, Susan Pear (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Wickersham gallery, 1970 (Box 5)
- Merida, Carlos, 1891-1985 (5 slides) (Box 5)
  - Jackson gallery, 1966 (Box 5)
- Merkin, Richard Marshall, b. 1938 (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Byron gallery, 1967 (Box 5)
- Merola, Mario Virgilio, b. 1931 (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1968 (Box 5)
- Merz, Mario, 1925-2003 (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Weber gallery, 1971, 1973 (Box 5)
- Messagier, Jean, 1920-1999 (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - Lefebre gallery, 1966 (Box 5)
- Michaux (4 slides) (Box 5)
  - Cordier-Ekstrom gallery, 1965, 1966 (Box 5)
- Mieczkowski, Edwin, b. 1929 (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - Jackson gallery, 1965 (Box 5)
- Mikus, Eleanor (10 slides) (Box 5)
  - Grand Central Moderns, 1968 (Box 5)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1971, 1973 (Box 5)
- Miles, Jeanne, 1908-1999 (3 slides) [Slide box 30] (Box 5)
  - Grand Central Moderns, 1968 (Box 5)
- Milkowski (14 slides) (Box 5)
  - Tibor de Nagy gallery, 1966, 1967, 1968 (Box 5)
- Millanzi (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - Amel gallery, 1965 (Box 5)
- Miller, Brenda, b. 1941 (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - Weber gallery, 1972 (Box 5)
- Miller, Richard (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - Peridot gallery, 1966 (Box 5)
- Milne, David (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - Feigen gallery, 1971 (Box 5)
- Milow, Keith, b. 1945 (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - Feigen gallery, 1971 (Box 5)
- Minujin, Marta, b. 1944 (10 slides) (Box 5)
  - Bianchini gallery, 1966 (Box 5)
- Mio, Kozo (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Bonino gallery, 1971 (Box 5)
- Mirto (10 slides) (Box 5)
  - Galerie International, 1968 (Box 5)
- Miscellaneous (17 slides) (Box 5)
  - "Home," 1968 (Box 5)
  - "Tice's," 1968 (Box 5)
  - "Building on Madison Ave.," 1968 (Box 5)
- Mischenet (5 slides) (Box 5)
  - Cordier-Ekstrom gallery, 1969 (Box 5)
- Mishaan, Rodolfo, b. 1924 (11 slides) (Box 5)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1968 (Box 5)
- Mitchell, Joan, 1926-1992 (10 slides) (Box 5)
  - Stable gallery, 1965 (Box 5)
  - M. Jackson gallery, 1968 (Box 5)
  - Xavier Fourcade gallery, 1980, 1981, 1982 (Box 5)
- Mitchell, Sue (5 slides) (Box 5)
  - Bodley gallery, 1966 (Box 5)
- Mittendorf, George (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - Zabriskie gallery, 1971 (Box 5)
- Miyashita (14 slides) (Box 5)
  - Grand Central Moderns, 1966 (Box 5)
  - Sachs gallery, 1967, 1969 (Box 5)
- Mogensen (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Bykert gallert, 1969 (Box 5)
- Moholy-Nagy, Laszlo, 1894-1946 (2 slides) (Box 5)
  - Wise gallery, 1970 (Box 5)
- Molinari, Guido, b. 1933 (4 slides) (Box 5)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1967 (Box 5)
- Moller (also Möller) (8 slides) (Box 5)
  - Midtown gallery, 1966, 1967, 1968 (Box 5)
- Monowitz (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - Arras gallery, 1973 (Box 5)
- Moore, Henry, 1898-1986 (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - Lincoln Center sculptures, 1973 (Box 5)
- Moore, Ken, b. 1923 (4 slides) (Box 5)
  - Wickersham gallery, 1969 (Box 5)
- Moore, John (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1973 (Box 5)
- Morales (5 slides) (Box 5)
  - Bonino gallery, 1966 (Box 5)
- Morley, Malcolm, b. 1931 (5 slides) (Box 5)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1969 (Box 5)
- Morofsky (8 slides) (Box 5)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1967, 1968, 1970 (Box 5)
- Morrell, Eugene (8 slides) (Box 5)
  - Bodley gallery, 1966 (Box 5)
- Morris, Carl, 1911-1993 (3 slides) (Box 5)
  - Kraushaar gallery, 1967 (Box 5)
- Morris, Robert, b. 1931 (13 slides) (Box 5)
  - Feigen gallery, 1965 (Box 5)
  - Feigen gallery, 1965 (Box 5)
  - Castelli gallery, 1968, 1969 (Box 5)
- Morse, Tiger (6 slides) (Box 5)
  - Greenross gallery, 1965 (Box 5)
- Moses, Grandma, 1860-1961 (4 slides) (Box 5)
  - Hammer gallery, 1971 (Box 5)
- Moskowitz, Robert, b. 1935 (1 slide) (Box 5)
  - Hoffman gallery, 1973 (Box 5)
- Moss, Irene (16 slides) (Box 5)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1966, 1968, 1969 (Box 5)
- Moss, Milton (4 slides) [Slide box 31] (Box 6)
  - Wickersham gallery, 1969 (Box 6)
- Moyer, Roy, 1921-2007 (3 slides) (Box 6)
  - Contemporaries gallery, 1964 (Box 6)
  - Midtown gallery, 1966 (Box 6)
- Moynihan, Rodrigo, 1910-1990 (12 slides) (Box 6)
  - de Nagy gallery, 1968, 1971 (Box 6)
- Mueller, George Ludwig, b. 1929 (7 slides) (Box 6)
  - Grippi-Waddell gallery, 1965, 1967 (Box 6)
- Mueller, Stephen, b. 1947 (7 slides) (Box 6)
  - Feigen gallery, 1971 (Box 6)
  - de Nagy gallery, 1971, 1973 (Box 6)
- Munari, Bruno, 1907-1998 (7 slides) (Box 6)
  - Wise gallery, 1966 (Box 6)
- Murray, Elizabeth, b. 1940 (10 slides) (Box 6)
  - Paula Cooper gallery, 1980, 1981, 1982, 1983, 1984 (Box 6)
- Myers, Charles (1 slide) (Box 6)
  - West Broadway gallery, 1973 (Box 6)
- Nadler, Harry (2 slides) (Box 6)
  - Schaeffer gallery, 1972 (Box 6)
- Nakagawa (2 slides) (Box 6)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1972, 1974 (Box 6)
- Napper, John, b. 1916 (1 slide) (Box 6)
  - Larcada gallery, 1970 (Box 6)
- Narbona, Jose Pla (Pla-Narbona, Josep, b. 1928) (3 slides) (Box 6)
  - Dintenfass gallery, 1969 (Box 6)
- Natkin, Robert, b. 1930 (33 slides) (Box 6)
  - Poindexter gallery, 1967, 1968 (Box 6)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1971, 1973 (Box 6)
  - Gimpel gallery, 1984 (Box 6)
- Nauman, Bruce, b. 1941 (6 slides) (Box 6)
  - Castelli Warehouse gallery, 1968, 1969 (Box 6)
- Neal, Reginald (14 slides) (Box 6)
  - Alem gallery, 1965, 1966 (Box 6)
  - Sachs gallery, 1968, 1969 (Box 6)
- Neel, Alice, 1900-1984 (36 slides) (Box 6)
  - R Miller gallery, 1984 (Box 6)
  - Graham gallery, 1968 (Box 6)
  - Various Portraits, dated from 1941-1984 (Box 6)
- Negret, Edgar, b. 1920 (5 slides) (Box 6)
  - Bonino gallery, 1969, 1972 (Box 6)
- Nelson, Jack (11 slides) (Box 6)
  - Krasner gallery, 1965, 1966, 1968 (Box 6)
- Nesbitt, Lowell, 1933-199 (10 slides) (Box 6)
  - Iolas gallery, 1964 (Box 6)
  - Byron gallery, 1964 (Box 6)
  - Stable gallery, 1969, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Stefanotty gallery, 1973 (Box 6)
- Nevelson, Louise, 1899-1988 (34 slides) (Box 6)
  - Pace gallery, 1964, 1966, 1968, 1969, 1970, 1971, 1984 (Box 6)
  - Jackson gallery, 1965 (Box 6)
- Newman, Daniel (11 slides) [Slide box 32] (Box 6)
  - Grippi-Waddell gallery, 1966 (Box 6)
- Nice, Don, b. 1932 (12 slides) (Box 6)
  - Allan Stone gallery, 1969, 1971 (Box 6)
- Niemczyc (3 slides) (Box 6)
  - Bodley gallery, 1969 (Box 6)
- Nivola, Constantino, 1911-1987 (10 slides) (Box 6)
  - Byron gallery, 1966 (Box 6)
- Nizuma (10 slides) (Box 6)
  - Wise gallery, 1965, 1966, 1968 (Box 6)
- Noé, Louis Felipe, b. 1933 (6 slides) (Box 6)
  - Bonino gallery, 1966 (Box 6)
- Noel, Georges, b. 1924 (2 slides) (Box 6)
  - Pace gallery, 1973 (Box 6)
- Noel, Michael (14 slides) (Box 6)
  - Wise gallery, 1965 (Box 6)
- Noguchi, Isamu, 1904-1988 (14 slides) (Box 6)
  - Cordier-Ekstrom gallery, 1964, 1968, 1970 (Box 6)
- Noland, Kenneth, b. 1924 (24 slides) (Box 6)
  - Parke Bernet gallery, 1964 (Box 6)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1966, 1967, 1971, 1973 (Box 6)
  - Rubin gallery, 1969, 1970 (Box 6)
- Norfolk, Geoffrey (1 slide) (Box 6)
  - de Nagy gallery, 1972 (Box 6)
- Norman, James (1 slide) (Box 6)
  - Westerly gallery, 1964 (Box 6)
- Notarberatolo (1 slide) (Box 6)
  - Amel gallery, 1965 (Box 6)
- Novak, Giora (25 slides) (Box 6)
  - Poindexter gallery, 1966, 1967, 1968 (Box 6)
- Novros, David, b. 1941 (10 slides) (Box 6)
  - Dwan gallery, 1967 (Box 6)
  - Bykert gallery, 1969, 1971 (Box 6)
- Nowack, W. (2 slides) (Box 6)
  - Allan Stone gallery, 1964 (Box 6)
- Noyes, David (1 slide) (Box 6)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1971 (Box 6)
- Obering, Mary (1 slide) (Box 6)
  - Weber gallery, 1972 (Box 6)
- Oceanic Art Exhibitions (65 slides) (Box 6)
  - Royal Marks gallery, 1969 (Box 6)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1972 (Box 6)
- Ochicwbo (4 slides) (Box 6)
  - Krasner gallery, 1965 (Box 6)
- Odate, Toshio (2 slides) (Box 6)
  - Radich gallery, 1969 (Box 6)
- Offner, Elliot, b. 1931 (3 slides) (Box 6)
  - Forum gallery, 1964 (Box 6)
- Ohlson, Douglas Dean, b. 1936 (14 slides) (Box 6)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1968, 1969, 1972 (Box 6)
- Olenska (6 slides) (Box 6)
  - Bodley gallery, 1964 (Box 6)
- Olitski, Jules, 1922-2007 (14 slides) (Box 6)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1966, 1968, 1971 (Box 6)
- On First Gallery (1 slide) (Box 6)
  - 1968 (Box 6)
- Oppenheim, Dennis, b. 1938 (1 slide) [Slide box 33] (Box 6)
  - Dwan gallery, 1968 (Box 6)
- Opper, John, b. 1908 (25 slides) (Box 6)
  - Borgenight gallery, 1966, 1968, 1971, 1973, 1980, 1982, 1983 (Box 6)
- Orellana, Gaston, b. 1933 (3 slides) (Box 6)
  - M. Jackson gallery, 1967 (Box 6)
- Ortlip, Paul (1 slide) (Box 6)
  - Wickersham gallery, 1969 (Box 6)
- Ortman, George Earl, b. 1926 (20 slides) (Box 6)
  - Parke-Benet gallery, 1964 (Box 6)
  - Wise gallery, 1966, 1967, 1969 (Box 6)
  - Gimpel gallery, 1972 (Box 6)
- Ossorio, Alfonso A., 1916-1990 (28 slides) (Box 6)
  - Cordier-Ekstrom gallery, 1964, 1965, 1967, 1968, 1972 (Box 6)
- Oster (11 slides) (Box 6)
  - Wise gallery, 1965, 1966 (Box 6)
- Ostlihn (2 slides) (Box 6)
  - Tibor de Nagy gallery, 1966 (Box 6)
- Ott, Jerry Duane, b. 1947 (1 slide) (Box 6)
  - Meisel gallery, 1973 (Box 6)
- Owen, Frank, b. 1939 (Box 6)
  - French and Co. gallery, 1971 (Box 6)
- Owens, Warren (4 slides) (Box 6)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1973, 1975 (Box 6)
- Pace, Stephen, b. 1918 (5 slides) (Box 6)
  - Graham gallery, 1969, 1974 (Box 6)
- Pacheco (8 slides) (Box 6)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1965 (Box 6)
  - Lee Ault gallery, 1971 (Box 6)
- Pachner, William, b. 1915 (5 slides) (Box 6)
  - Krasner gallery, 1967 (Box 6)
- Padovano (6 slides) (Box 6)
  - Schaeffer gallery, 1968, 1970 (Box 6)
- Paik, Nam June, 1932-2006 (2 slides0 (Box 6)
  - Bonino gallery, 1965 (Box 6)
- Palatnik, Abraham, b. 1928 (4 slides) (Box 6)
  - Wise gallery, 1965, 1970 (Box 6)
- Pardozzi (1 slide) (Box 6)
  - Cordier-Ekstrom gallery, 1972 (Box 6)
- Parker, Raymond, 1922-1990 (12 slides) (Box 6)
  - Rubin gallery, 1969 (Box 6)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1970, 1971, 1973 (Box 6)
- Parker, Robert Andrew, b. 1927 (5 slides) (Box 6)
  - Dintenfass gallery, 1969 (Box 6)
- Parsons, Betty Bierne, 1900-1982 (3 slides) (Box 6)
  - Grand Central Moderns, 1967 (Box 6)
- Paschke, Edward, 1939-2004 (2 slides) (Box 6)
  - 100 Acres gallery, 1971 (Box 6)
- Pashgian, Helen, b. 1934 (10 slides) (Box 6)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1969, 1972 (Box 6)
- Pasilis (3 slides) (Box 6)
  - Great Jones gallery, 1966 (Box 6)
- Paternostro, Cesar (7 slides) (Box 6)
  - Sachs gallery, 1968, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Denise René gallery, 1973 (Box 6)
- Pavlos (5 slides) (Box 6)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1967 (Box 6)
- Pearlstein, Philip, b. 1924 (4 slides) (Box 6)
  - Frumkin gallery, 1969 (Box 6)
- Pearson, Henry, 1914-2006 (6 slides) (Box 6)
  - Radich gallery, 1965, 1966 (Box 6)
- Pearson, John, b. 1940 (1 slide) [Slide box 34] (Box 6)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1971 (Box 6)
- Pease, David (2 slides) (Box 6)
  - Dintenfass gallery, 1971 (Box 6)
- Periera, I. Rice (1 slide) (Box 6)
  - "Oblique Progression," 1948 (Box 6)
- Perlman, Joel, b. 1943 (1 slide) (Box 6)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1973 (Box 6)
- Perr, Herbert (5 slides) (Box 6)
  - Myers gallery, 1970, 1972 (Box 6)
- Perrin (2 slides) (Box 6)
  - Rose Fried gallery, 1964 (Box 6)
- Perry, Charles O. (2 slides) (Box 6)
  - Waddell gallery, 1968 (Box 6)
- Peruvian Art (Ancient) (8 slides) (Box 6)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1968 (Box 6)
- Pettet, William, b. 1942 (2 slides) (Box 6)
  - Elkon gallery, 1969 (Box 6)
- Pettibone, Richard, b. 1938 (12 slides) (Box 6)
  - Castelli gallery, 1969 (Box 6)
- Pettibone, Shirley, b. 1938 (3 slides) (Box 6)
  - 100 Acres gallery, 1973 (Box 6)
- Peugh, B. (2 slides) (Box 6)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1971 (Box 6)
- Pfaff, Judy, b. 1946 (4 slides) (Box 6)
  - Holly Solomon gallery, 1973, 1981, 1982 (Box 6)
- Pfahler, Georg Karl, b. 1926 (4 slides) (Box 6)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1966 (Box 6)
- Phillips (1 slide) (Box 6)
  - AFA, 1966 (Box 6)
- Phillips, Peter, b. 1939 (5 slides) (Box 6)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1968 (Box 6)
- Piagentino, Gianni (1 slide) (Box 6)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1971 (Box 6)
- Picelj, Ivan, b. 1924 (10 slides) (Box 6)
  - Wise gallery, 1965 (Box 6)
- Picillo, Joseph (2 slides) (Box 6)
  - Banfer gallery, 1966 (Box 6)
- Pickens (12 slides) (Box 6)
  - Rehn gallery, 1967 (Box 6)
- Piene, Otto, b. 1928 (7 slides) (Box 6)
  - Wise gallery, 1969 (Box 6)
- Pierce, Waldo, 1884-1970 (2 slides) (Box 6)
  - Midtown gallery, 1966 (Box 6)
- Pini (18 slides) (Box 6)
  - Jason gallery, 1967 (Box 6)
- Pistoletto, Michelangelo, b. 1933 (11 slides) (Box 6)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1967, 1969 (Box 6)
- Plagens, Peter, b. 1941 (3 slides) (Box 6)
  - Reese Palley gallery, 1971 (Box 6)
- Platt (2 slides) (Box 6)
  - Bodley gallery, 1969 (Box 6)
- Polesello, Rogelio, b. 1939 (2 slides) (Box 6)
  - Bonino gallery, 1 (Box 6)
- Polhemus, Lisa, fl. 1960- (5 slides) (Box 6)
  - Bodley gallery, 1969 (Box 6)
- Poliakoff, Serge, 1906-1969 (6 slides) (Box 6)
  - Lefebre gallery, 1968, 1971 (Box 6)
- Pollack, Reginald (5 slides) (Box 6)
  - Peridot gallery, 1969 (Box 6)
- Pollock, Jackson, 1912-1956 (1 slide) (Box 6)
  - "Number 27," 1950 (Box 6)
- Pomeroy, Florence W., 1890-1981 (2 slides) (Box 6)
  - Bodley gallery, 1968 (Box 6)
- Pomodoro (2 slides) (Box 6)
  - Jackson gallery, 1971 (Box 6)
- Pond, Clayton, b. 1941 (7 slides) (Box 6)
  - Jackson gallery, 1968 (Box 6)
- Pone, Joan (2 slides) (Box 6)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1970 (Box 6)
- Poons, Larry, b. 1937 (22 slides) (Box 6)
  - Green gallery, 1965 (Box 6)
  - AFA, 1966 (Box 6)
  - Castelli gallery, 1968 (Box 6)
  - Rubin gallery, 1970, 1971, 1973 (Box 6)
- Poor, Anne, b. 1918 (4 slides) (Box 6)
  - Graham gallery, 1971 (Box 6)
- Popovic, Misa, b. 1925 (1 slide) (Box 6)
  - Bodley gallery, 1971 (Box 6)
- Porter, David, b. 1912 (6 slides) (Box 6)
  - Circ. Lib. Ptg., 1966 (Box 6)
- Porter, Fairfield, 1907-1975 (22 slides) [Slide box 35] (Box 6)
  - Tibor de Nagy gallery, 1967, 1968, 1969, 1970 (Box 6)
- Porter, Katherine, b. 1941 (3 slides) (Box 6)
  - McKee gallery, 1981, 1982, 1983 (Box 6)
- Posen, Stephen, b. 1939 (2 slides) (Box 6)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1971, 1974 (Box 6)
- Posnakoff, Yanni (3 slides) (Box 6)
  - Walter gallery, 1969 (Box 6)
- Potts, Don, b. 1936 (1 slide) (Box 6)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1966 (Box 6)
- Poulos, Basilious Nicholas, b. 1941 (1 slide) (Box 6)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1972 (Box 6)
- Powers, Richard (6 slides) (Box 6)
  - Rehn gallery, 1968 (Box 6)
- Pozzi (11 slides) (Box 6)
  - XX Cent. West gallery, 1967 (Box 6)
- Prado, Nadine (3 slides) (Box 6)
  - Mizrachi gallery, 1971 (Box 6)
- Preminger, Mary G., 1918-1996 (5 slides) (Box 6)
  - Grand Central Moderns, 1967 (Box 6)
- Prestini, James, 1908-1993 (3 slides) (Box 6)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1971 (Box 6)
- Prestopino, Gregorio, 1907-1994 (8 slides) (Box 6)
  - Amel gallery, 1964 (Box 6)
  - Dintenfass gallery, 1966 (Box 6)
- Price, Inge (4 slides) (Box 6)
  - Bodley gallery, 1967 (Box 6)
- Programmed Art Exhibition (16 slides) (Box 6)
  - Various Artists (Box 6)
  - Loeb Gallery, NYU, 1964 (Box 6)
- Pupp, Gisbert (10 slides) (Box 6)
  - Ange gallery, 1969 (Box 6)
- Querido (9 slides) (Box 6)
  - Bodley gallery, 1965 (Box 6)
- Quaytman, Harvey, 1937-2000 (5 slides) (Box 6)
  - Royal Marks gallery, 1966 (Box 6)
  - Paula Cooper gallery, 1971 (Box 6)
- Rabkin, Leo, b. 1919 (4 slides) (Box 6)
  - Feigen gallery, 1965, 1967 (Box 6)
- Raffael, Joseph, b. 1933 (see also Raphael, Joseph) (9 slides) (Box 6)
  - Stable gallery, 1968 (Box 6)
  - Hoffman gallery, 1973 (Box 6)
- Raisen (1 slide) (Box 6)
  - Wise gallery, 1964 (Box 6)
- Ramirez (10 slides) (Box 6)
  - Graham gallery, 1966 (Box 6)
- Rand, Archie, b. 1949 (2 slides) (Box 6)
  - de Nagy gallery, 1972 (Box 6)
- Randell, Richard (also Randall) (5 slides) (Box 6)
  - Royal Marks gallery, 1968, 1969, 1971 (Box 6)
- Raphael, Joseph (see also Raffael, Joseph) (3 slides) (Box 6)
  - Palley gallery, 1972 (Box 6)
- Rauschenberg, Robert, b. 1925 (35 slides) (Box 6)
  - Castelli gallery, 1965, 1967, 1969, 1971, 1973, 1974 (Box 6)
  - Sonnabend gallery, 1970 (Box 6)
- Ray, Man, 1890-1976 (23 slides) (Box 6)
  - Cordier-Ekstrom gallery, 1965, 1968, 1970 (Box 6)
- Raymo, Anne, b. 1939 (4 slides) [Slide box 36] (Box 6)
  - Dintenfass gallery, 1969, 1972 (Box 6)
- Raynes (1 slide) (Box 6)
  - Bodley gallery, 1969 (Box 6)
- Raynor (2 slides) (Box 6)
  - Sachs gallery, 1968 (Box 6)
- Rayo, Omar, b. 1928 (18 slides) (Box 6)
  - Bonino gallery, 1964 (Box 6)
  - Contemporaries gallery, 1965 (Box 6)
- Raysse, Martial, b. 1936 (13 slides) (Box 6)
  - Iolas gallery, 1964, 1966 (Box 6)
  - Dwan gallery, 1965 (Box 6)
- Reed, Paul, b. 1919 (11 slides) (Box 6)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1965, 1966 (Box 6)
  - Schaeffer gallery, 1971 (Box 6)
- Reginato, Peter, b. 1945 (1 slide) (Box 6)
  - de Nagy gallery, 1971 (Box 6)
- Reibeck (9 slides) (Box 6)
  - Wise gallery, 1966 (Box 6)
- Reich (4 slides) (Box 6)
  - Bodley gallery, 1969 (Box 6)
- Reich, Murray, b. 1932 (1 slide) (Box 6)
  - Hutchinson gallery, 1972 (Box 6)
- Reichner, Ann (2 slides) (Box 6)
  - Bodley gallery, 1971 (Box 6)
- Reid (4 slides) (Box 6)
  - Grand Central Moderns, 1966 (Box 6)
- Reinhaud (8 slides) (Box 6)
  - Lefebre gallery, 1966, 1970, 1972 (Box 6)
- Remington (3 slides) (Box 6)
  - Bykert gallery, 1967 (Box 6)
- Rennels, Sig (1 slide) (Box 6)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1973 (Box 6)
- Rennie, Helen Sewell, ca. 1906-1989 (4 slides) (Box 6)
  - Bridge gallery, 1965 (Box 6)
- Renouf, Edward Pechmann, b. 1906 (3 slides) (Box 6)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1971 (Box 6)
- Resika, Paul, b. 1928 (15 slides) (Box 6)
  - Peridot gallery, 1968, 1969, 1970 (Box 6)
- Reynolds, William (1 slide) (Box 6)
  - Pace gallery, 1965 (Box 6)
- Rice, Dan, b. 1926 (10 slides) (Box 6)
  - Viviano gallery, 1966 (Box 6)
- Rich, Garry, b. 1943 (3 slides) (Box 6)
  - Hutchinson gallery, 1972 (Box 6)
- Richer, Ira, b. 1947 (6 slides) (Box 6)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1970 (Box 6)
- Richter (2 slides) (Box 6)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1968 (Box 6)
- Richter, Hans, 1888-1976 (10 slides) (Box 6)
  - Byron gallery, 1968 (Box 6)
- Rickey, George, 1907-2002 (7 slides) (Box 6)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1967 (Box 6)
- Riese, Beatrice, 1917-2004 (2 slides) (Box 6)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1969 (Box 6)
- Rifka, Judy, b. 1945 (11 slides) (Box 6)
  - Brooke Alexander gallery, 1982, 1983, 1984 (Box 6)
- Rikko (5 slides) (Box 6)
  - Bodley gallery, 1967 (Box 6)
- Riley, Bridget, b. 1931 (47 slides) (Box 6)
  - Feigen gallery, 1965, 1966, 1967 (Box 6)
- Ringi (4 slides) [Slide box 37] (Box 7)
  - Bodley gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
- Rinke, Klaus, b. 1939 (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Reese Palley gallery, 1972 (Box 7)
- Rivera (5 slides) (Box 7)
  - Matisse gallery, 1966 (Box 7)
- Rivers, Larry, 1923-2002 (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Graham gallery, 1969 (Box 7)
- Robertson-Swann, Ron (3 slides) (Box 7)
  - Schaeffer gallery, 1971 (Box 7)
- Robinson, Jay (20 slides) (Box 7)
  - XX Cent West gallery, 1966, 1967, 1968 (Box 7)
- Robus, Hugo, 1885-1964 (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - Forum gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
- Rockburne, Dorothea, b. 1932 (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Bykert gallery, 1972 (Box 7)
- Rodriguez-Lorrain (11 slides) (Box 7)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1965 (Box 7)
- Rogovin, Milton, b. 1909 (also Rogouin) (3 slides) (Box 7)
  - Babcock gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
- Rohm, Robert, b. 1934 (4 slides) (Box 7)
  - O.K. Harris, 1972, 1973 (Box 7)
- Rohr, Robert (3 slides) (Box 7)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1971 (Box 7)
- Rolick (4 slides) (Box 7)
  - Amel gallery, 1965 (Box 7)
- Rombolo (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Barney-Weinger gallery, 1972 (Box 7)
- Rome, Harold, 1908-1993 (3 slides) (Box 7)
  - Bodley gallery, 1970 (Box 7)
- Romano, Salvatore Michael, b. 1925 (5 slides) (Box 7)
  - Sachs gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
  - Hutchinson gallery, 1973 (Box 7)
- Roos, Gabriel (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - West Broadway gallery, 1973 (Box 7)
- Rosan, Larry (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1973 (Box 7)
- Ruscha, Edward, b. 1937 (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - Pace gallery, 1965 (Box 7)
- Rose, William, b. 1930 (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Braverman gallery, 1966 (Box 7)